[{
        "question": "Cloud computing is a ..............",
        "option1": "reliable system",
        "option2": "stateless system",
        "option3": "stateful system",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "stateless system"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which option is related to service provided by Cloud ?",
        "option1": "AaaS",
        "option2": "Reliability",
        "option3": "Sourcing",
        "option4": "Ownership",
        "answer": "Sourcing"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. is the essential concept related to Cloud?",
        "option1": "Reliability",
        "option2": "Abstraction",
        "option3": "Productivity",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Abstraction"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can be identified as cloud?",
        "option1": "Intranet",
        "option2": "Hadoop",
        "option3": "Web Applications",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "Hadoop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following option is the IaaS service provider?",
        "option1": "EC1",
        "option2": "EC2",
        "option3": "EC10",
        "option4": "Hybrid",
        "answer": "EC2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the most important area of concern in cloud computing?",
        "option1": "Storage",
        "option2": "Scalability",
        "option3": "Security",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Security"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following feature allows you to optimize your system and capture all possible transactions?",
        "option1": "elasticity",
        "option2": "scalability",
        "option3": "reliability",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "elasticity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is surely an impediment to established businesses starting new enterprises?",
        "option1": "Capitalization",
        "option2": "Proposition",
        "option3": "Globalization",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Capitalization"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest degree of integration in cloud computing?",
        "option1": "AaaS",
        "option2": "SaaS",
        "option3": "PaaS",
        "option4": "CaaS",
        "answer": "SaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a major cloud computing platform?",
        "option1": "Microsoft Azure",
        "option2": "Amazon EC2",
        "option3": "IBM Deep Blue",
        "option4": "Google 101",
        "answer": "IBM Deep Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Private cloud is a -",
        "option1": "A cloud service inaccessible to anyone but the cultural elite",
        "option2": "standard cloud service offered via the Internet",
        "option3": "cloud architecture maintained within an enterprise data center.",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "cloud architecture maintained within an enterprise data center."
    },
    {
        "question": "Cloud Foundry is a -",
        "option1": "industry wide PaaS initiative",
        "option2": "VMware-led open source PaaS",
        "option3": "factory that produces cloud components",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "VMware-led open source PaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following services that need to be negotiated in Service Level Agreements?",
        "option1": "Logging",
        "option2": "Auditing",
        "option3": "Regulatory compliance",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following option allows different operating systems to run in their own memory space?",
        "option1": "VMC",
        "option2": "VMS",
        "option3": "VMM",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "VMM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following service provider provides the least amount of built-in security?",
        "option1": "SaaS",
        "option2": "PaaS",
        "option3": "IaaS",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "IaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct statement",
        "option1": "Platforms represent nearly the full cloud software stack",
        "option2": "A platform in the cloud is a software layer that is used to create higher levels of service",
        "option3": "Platforms often come replete with tools and utilities to aid in application design and deployment",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a major type of cloud computing usage?",
        "option1": "Platform as a Service",
        "option2": "Software as a Service",
        "option3": "Hardware as a Service",
        "option4": "Infrastructure as a Service",
        "answer": "Hardware as a Service"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following type of virtualization is also characteristic of cloud computing?",
        "option1": "Storage",
        "option2": "Application",
        "option3": "CPU",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "The technology used to distribute service requests to resources is referred to as:",
        "option1": "Load performing",
        "option2": "Load scheduling",
        "option3": "Load balancing",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Load balancing"
    }, {
        "question": "Point out the correct statement:",
        "option1": "A client can request access to a cloud service from any location",
        "option2": "A cloud has multiple application instances and directs requests to an instance based on conditions",
        "option3": "Computers can be partitioned into a set of virtual machines with each machine being assigned a workload",
        "option4": "All of the mentioned",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned"
    }
]